<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Life Coach & Mindfulness Teacher]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Life Coach & Mindfulness Teacher]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 May 2016 03:19:33 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="undefinedrss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>A life coach, spiritual teacher, and meditation guide, Rina G. Singh has developed her meditation techniques and traditions through professional studies in coaching, energy healing, and mindfulness practice. For more than a decade, Rina has served around the world, guiding people as they search for peace, joy, happiness, love, empowerment, and reconnection of the outer world with the internal matrix. She is renowned for her personalized methods, designed to work with people regardless of past experiences with spiritual practice and taking into account all of the minute details that come to make up an individual personality. Rina believes that the ultimate source of human potential is in the inner life source, mind, and body. She has done extensive coaching and spiritual work, drawing from this work evidence to back up this belief. With Rina’s meditation approach, coaching and energy healing techniques arise naturally and comfortably, leading to deeper, lasting transformations with an aim toward mental clarity and emotional freedom. Guiding meditation sessions that are dynamic, engaging, and positively effective, Rina can show you the pathway to true discovery, transformation, and abundant love. Connect with Rina </p>]]></description>
            <link>undefineda-life-coach-spiritual-teacher-and-meditation-guide-rina/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">89bf8cf4-1808-4ab9-8614-a6a37868a679</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2016 03:19:32 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>